I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
"Middle Schooler Ai Yamaguchi
to be youngest Triple Crown winner?"
You heard of Beck?
Never heard of them.
I'll go get us some drinks.
Beck, huh?
Koyuki...Let's do it!
I'm alright. I can do this!
One, two...
Typhoon! Typhoon 24! 24-7, non-stop!
We're gonna rush at you!
Gonna send you flyin'!
Lift up your heavy ass, now
If you take off that stiff head
you'll feel totally loose
This crazy, crazy world
You just have to Stage Dive or Die
Mind blower, a shower of sweat
Run towards a new world, my life
Those who seek it will be rewarded
Pass the hot shot,
keep on coming, come on!
Blow your mind
Squeeze your sweat yeah
-Blow your mind
-Koyuki! Look up, will you?!
-Squeeze your sweat
Find the way you are,
-spice of your life
-Yeah!
Heavy beat, hey come on people
Find the way you are,
spice of your life
Heavy beat, hey come on people yeah
Take your spice yeah
Find my wife
-It's no good.
-Huh?
Look at them. They're all
just holding up the walls.
I don't know...
At this rate, they may
be better off with Togo.
What do you think, sis?
Yeah!
Put your hands up, up, up, up!
Yeah, check it out!
Let's go concrete hell,
human safari park escape
Ape in the brain,
mass brain-washing operation,
no thank you
Let's walk together, step in step,
and we'll get stuck in the deep
We're at the rebellious age,
free as we go
This is no barrier, just what is important,
nothing impure, just clear
No pressure at our pace,
I'm not joining that race
Yo! Still got complaints?
We're fools, just fools,
but everyone's a top-class mother fucker
Fly with god of wind,
here we go all amigos
"Triple Crown event planned.
Appearance in TV drama soon..."
here we go all amigos
"Triple Crown event planned.
Appearance in TV drama soon..."
Who? Who? Foojin, takes me cruisin'
"Triple Crown event planned.
Appearance in TV drama soon..."
Music that cuts through the wind,
"Triple Crown event planned.
Appearance in TV drama soon..."
free form
"Triple Crown event planned.
Appearance in TV drama soon..."
Who? Who? Foojin
I'm really holding everybody back...
My guitar-playing sucks...
But Ryusuke said you did well
for a first-timer.
Maybe Saku did,
but my guitar was the worst...
I'll bet he'll never ask me again.
Koyuki, do you have something
around your neck?
This? I always have it on.
You never noticed it?
No...
See. It's Eddy's pick-the one you gave me.
It's my good luck charm.
Maho...This song...
Oh, that...
It's a new song. It's still unfinished.
The one recorded after our performance?
True, it's a nice song,
but Chiba's voice is too "punk" to sing it.
I'll never sing a gloomy song like that!
Hello...
Um...
Yo!
That song...Won't you let me sing it?
-Huh?!
Ryusuke-kun...Does this song have a title?
Yeah, but just a tentative one.
I call it "Face."
This song...It's about Maho, isn't it?
Mhm...
Large lips keeping motion,
trying to keep blaming on
When I say reason I'm late on
Find you turning, laughing and smiling
Sing it up,
-my sister
-Huh?
In this world which everyone is lonely
Everything will be fine someday
Some other day
Not bad!
Taira-kun! What now?! Are you
still against letting Koyuki join?
Jesus Christ...
No. I'm not against it.
It's true, when Ryusuke first
wanted to let Koyuki in,
I thought it was too soon.
And you can't say he did well
at our live performance.
But I'm sure of it now.
This band is gonna make it big.
Of course, we'll never
make it as we are now.
There are countless other bands
out there. So how do we make it?
I had absolutely no idea...
But...after listening to
Koyuki's song just now, I got it.
That's right.
If we set a spark to the chemistry
the five of us have, we can do it!
-"The...
...five of us?"
You guys're part of Beck, too!
By any chance, with a new vocalist
on board...Am I fired?
Idiot! Without you, our live shows
won't have any excitement!
I can play the guitar, you know!
I can do Big Blue Hearts or Crush...
Ryusuke-chan? You listening?
Hey...
-They're working real hard.
-Yeah.
Koyuki...You gotta work harder...
Boy, that all-nighter
on Saturday was rough...
When I got home, I just zonked out.
And I broke my sleep record.
Saku, have you heard
Dying Breed's new song?
I heard it on an FM station.
It sure is a great song.
I sort of learned it by ear.
Let's go, Saku...
Those guys...
Fooling around with that guitar...
He's gotten too big for his britches
ever since that swim meet.
Did you recognize it? That song...
"I Call You Love."
It's Dying Breed's newest song.
Huh? What?
A live house?
There's no way!
But, I'm going to sing...
Well, you know...
The kind of music I like is...
The Beatles and the Yardbirds...
and the early Stones.
And the Rocket Boys!
Yeah, I know, but...
Sorry, but I have absolutely
no interest in anything
other than British beat
from the good old days.
That's too bad...I wanted you
to hear my singing.
I guess the only one who'll come...
is Momoko-sensei, I guess.
I'll come!
I'll pay you 1000 yen an hour,
so please bring Momoko-sensei!
Please! Please! Please!
Yukio...Yukio!
Oh, sorry!
Oh, it's you.
I heard from Masaru...
He says you're in a band.
Uh...We have a rehearsal,
so I've got to get going.
I don't give a damn about that.
But...
Hey...Let me play that guitar.
It's probably just a rinky-dink band.
What the hell is this?
You think you're so hot...
Hands off!
Damn you! Watch how you talk to me!
You'll pay for that...
Huh?
You'll pay for that!
So what're you gonna do, bastard?
Damn!
Damn you! I'll kill you!
Alright! That's enough!
-Can't stand to see anyone being bullied.
-Ray! Koyuki's in trouble!
Yeah. We're in the back street
near the parking.
-Yeah, yeah, hurry!
-Chiba-kun!
Koyuki, I like your spirit.
Who the hell are you?
I can't forgive thickheaded guys
who can't understand others' pain.
I just called them on my cell phone!
They'll be here soon!
Chiba-kun!
Just watch.
I hear Chiba was always bullied
when he was little.
Chiba!
Can you believe it? Until Chiba
learned karate, he was a crybaby.
That was a sucker kick...
Shut up! This one's for Koyuki!
Okay...
One, two, three!
-Yeah!
You're Ryusuke-kun
of Serial Mama, aren't you?
Huh?
My sempai is a friend
of bass player Yamagishi-kun.
He got me on the guest list once
and I went to see you.
I was impressed by your guitar.
You were a Japanese Jimmy Page!
I'll get even with you one of these days.
Sure! Any day!
Look at what he did...
Koyuki...Are you alright?
Yeah. I'm fine.
When Eddy comes to Japan,
I'll get something else of his for you.
Maho...
But I'm here to hear "Face" today.
-Do your best, now.
-Yeah.
Do you feel the pressure?
Not at all.
Alright!
Let's take that live house by storm!
-Yeah!
-Alright!
How's the bass?
-Can you bring it down some?
-You got it.
Let's do the guitar next.
-How is it?
-Yeah, that's about right.
"Dying Breed-Japan Visit Slated!!!"
Large lips in the motion,
trying to keep blaming on
"Dying Breed-Japan Visit Slated!!!"
As I say reason I'm late on
Find you turning, laughing and smiling
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
I got chilled and caught a cold.
"Next Episode"
Take care of yourselves, now.